BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6719: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Altoona Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Amalgamated Food Employees Union, Local 590, 1959-1965 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Item 3: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Altoona Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Amalgamated Food Employees Union, Local 590, 1963-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 7/14/1963 and expires on 9/11/1965. Covers 1250 workers in Cumberland, MD; LaVale, MD; PA
  - Code no.6752: Penn Fruit Co., Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 929, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Penn Fruit Co., Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 929, 1970-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 1/11/1970 and expires on 1/9/1972. Covers an unknown number of workers in Philadelphia, PA
  - Code no.6766: The Milwaukee Area Retail Meat Industry and The Milwaukee Area Meat Cutters Local 73, 1963-1972 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: The Milwaukee Area Retail Meat Industry and The Milwaukee Area Meat Cutters Local 73, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 10/6/1963 and expires on 10/1/1966. Covers 1100 workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 2: The Milwaukee Area Retail Meat Industry and The Milwaukee Area Meat Cutters Local 73, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 10/2/1966 and expires on 2/8/1969. Covers 1250 workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 3: The Milwaukee Area Retail Meat Industry and The Milwaukee Area Meat Cutters Local 73, 1972-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 2/13/1972 and expires on 2/17/1973. Covers 1250 workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 4: The Milwaukee Area Retail Meat Industry and The Milwaukee Area Meat Cutters Local 73, 1972-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1972 and expires on 12/31/1972. Covers an unknown number of workers in Milwaukee, WI
  - Code no.6733: Independent Super Markets and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1961-1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Independent Super Markets and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1961 and expires on 5/1/1963. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 2: Independent Super Markets and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1963-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1963 and expires on 5/1/1965. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 3: Independent Super Markets and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1965 and expires on 5/1/1968. Covers 3000 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 4: Independent Super Markets and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1968 and expires on 5/1/1971. Covers 3500 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 5: Independent Super Markets and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1971-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1971 and expires on 11/30/1973. Covers 3000 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 6: Independent Super Markets and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1973-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1973 and expires on 5/4/1974. Covers 6500 workers in St. Louis, MO
  - Code no.6796: Kroger and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1963-1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Kroger and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 12/29/1963 and expires on 5/1/1966. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 2: Kroger and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 5/2/1966 and expires on 5/3/1969. Covers 1000 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 3: Kroger and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1969-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 5/4/1969 and expires on 5/6/1972. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 4: Kroger and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1972-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 5/7/1972 and expires on 11/30/1973. Covers 1000 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 5: Kroger and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1973-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1973 and expires on 5/4/1974. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 6: Kroger and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 655, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 5/5/1974 and expires on 5/4/1976. Covers 1247 workers in St. Louis, MO
  - Code no.6732: Chain and Independent Food Stores and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 88, 1967- 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Chain and Independent Food Stores and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 88, 1967-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/29/1967 and expires on 1/25/1969. Covers 2100 workers in St. Louis, MO; St. Louis Co., MO; St. Charles, MO; Madison Co., IL
    - Item 2: Chain and Independent Food Stores and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 88, 1967-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1967 and expires on 12/31/1968. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO; St. Louis Co., MO; St. Charles, MO; Madison Co., IL
    - Item 3: Chain and Independent Food Stores and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 88, 1969-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/26/1969 and expires on 1/29/1972. Covers 2500 workers in St. Louis, MO; St. Louis Co., MO; St. Charles, MO; Madison Co., IL
    - Item 4: Chain and Independent Food Stores and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 88, 1972-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/30/1972 and expires on 1/26/1974. Covers 2400 workers in St. Louis, MO; St. Louis Co., MO; St. Charles, MO; Madison Co., IL
  - Code no.6734: No Employer and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 234, Hebrew Butcher Workers Union, 1968-1973 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: No Employer and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 234, Hebrew Butcher Workers Union, 1968-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 12/15/1968 and expires on 12/13/1970. Covers 1300 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 2: No Employer and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 234, Hebrew Butcher Workers Union, 1970-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 12/13/1970 and expires on 12/17/1972. Covers 1300 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 3: No Employer and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 234, Hebrew Butcher Workers Union, 1972-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 12/17/1972 and expires on 12/16/1973. Covers 1060 workers in New York, NY
  - Code no.6801: National Tea Co., Standard Grocery Division and Retail Clerks International Association Locals 725, 25, 1441, and 550, 1970- 1974 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: National Tea Co., Standard Grocery Division and Retail Clerks International Association Locals 725, 25, 1441, and 550, 1970-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 3/3/1970 and expires on 3/3/1973. Covers 1360 workers in Indiana
    - Item 2: National Tea Co., Standard Grocery Division and Retail Clerks International Association Locals 725, 25, 1441, and 550, 1973-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 3/4/1973 and expires on 3/2/1974. Covers 1125 workers in Indiana
  - Code no.6802: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 592, Affiliated with New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1967-1974 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 592, Affiliated with New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 11/12/1967. Covers an unknown number of workers in Massachusetts
    - Item 2: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 592, Affiliated with New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 6/29/1971 and expires on 1/12/1974. Covers 2400 workers in Massachusetts
  - Code no.6816: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 2, Affiliated with New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1970-1974 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 2, Affiliated with New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1970-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 3/20/1970 and expires on 9/16/1972. Covers 2000 workers in Massachusetts
    - Item 2: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 2, Affiliated with New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1972-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 9/17/1972 and expires on 1/12/1974. Covers 1785 workers in Massachusetts
    - Item 3: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 2, Affiliated with New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 1/13/1974 and expires on 1/11/1976. Covers an unknown number of workers in Massachusetts
  - Code no.6918: East Bay Motor Car Dealers, Inc. and Eastbay Automotive Council, 1960-1972 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: East Bay Motor Car Dealers, Inc. and Eastbay Automotive Council, 1960-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1960 and expires on 6/1/1965. Covers an unknown number of workers in Alameda Co., CA; Contra Costa Co., CA; San Joaquin Co., CA
    - Item 2: East Bay Motor Car Dealers, Inc. and Eastbay Automotive Council, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1962 and expires on 6/1/1965. Covers an unknown number of workers in Alameda Co., CA; Contra Costa Co., CA; San Joaquin Co., CA
    - Item 3: East Bay Motor Car Dealers, Inc. and Eastbay Automotive Council+K514, 1968-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1968 and expires on 6/1/1972. Covers an unknown number of workers in Alameda Co., CA; Contra Costa Co., CA; San Joaquin Co., CA
  - Code no.6781: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 1063 and 1657, Retail Clerks Union, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 1063 and 1657, Retail Clerks Union, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 5/5/1968 and expires on 5/8/1971. Covers 2720 workers in Atlanta, GA; Covington, GA; Decatur, GA; Marietta, GA; LaGrange, GA; Cartersville, GA; Athens, GA; Griffin, GA; Newnan, GA; Augusta, GA; Rome, GA; Carrollton, GA; Macon, GA; Colu
    - Item 2: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 1063 and 1657, Retail Clerks Union, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 5/9/1971 and expires on 5/11/1974. Covers 855 workers in Atlanta, GA; Covington, GA; Dalton, GA; Decatur, GA; Marietta, GA; LaGrange, GA; Cartersville, GA; Athens, GA; Griffin, GA; Newnan, GA; Augusta, GA; Rome, GA; Carrollton, GA; Mac
- Series X: Industry Code #45, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6505: Retail Stores of Tacoma and Retail Clerks International Association, Local 367, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Code no.6507: Bamberger's New Jersey and Department Store Employees Union, Local 21, R.C.I.A., 1959-1974 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Code no.6515: Seattle Department Stores Association, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 1207, Department Store Division, 1961- 1972 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Series XI: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.5002: Baltimore Transit Company and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1300, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Code no.5005: The Cincinnati Transit Company and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 627, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Code no.5008: The Connecticut Company and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America, Divisions 281, 425, 443, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Code no.5010: Eastern Massachusetts Street Railway Company and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 1509, 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Code no.5011: Fifth Avenue Coach Lines, Inc. and Transport Workers Union of America, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Code no.5012: Kansas City Public Service Company and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 1287, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Code no.5026: Virginia Transit Company Portsmouth Transit Company and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America, Divisions 1220, 1177, 1264, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Code no.5028: Meter Cab Operators and Individual Owners and Independent Meter Cab Operators of San Francisco and Chauffeurs' Union, Local 265, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Code no.5030: Yellow Cab Company of Los Angeles and Chauffeurs' Union, Local 640, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Code no.5031: Central-Southwestern Greyhound Lines, Greyhound Corporation and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America, Divisions 1126, 1150, 1313, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Code no.5034: Southern Greyhound Lines, Greyhound Corporation and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America, Divisions 1174, 1238, 1314, 1315, 1323, 1326, 1493, 1500, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Code no.5034: Southern Greyhound Lines, Greyhound Corporation and Amalgamated Transit Union, Divisions 1174, 1238, 1314, 1315, 1323, 1326, 1493, 1500, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Code no.5032: Central Greyhound Lines, Greyhound Corporation and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America, Divisions 1042, 1126, 1150, 1211, 1303, 1500, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Code no.5033: Greyhound Lines, Inc. and Amalgamated Transit Union, National Council of Greyhound Divisions 1042, 1043, 1063, 1098, 1126, 1150, 1174, 1201, 1202, 1203, 1205, 1210, 1211, 1238, 1303, 1313, 1314, 1315, 1323, 1326, 1493, 1500, 1516, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Code no.5035: Central-Southwestern Greyhound Lines, Greyhound Corporation and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 1313, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Code no.5037: Central Greyhound Lines, Greyhound Corporation and Amalgamated Transit Union, Divisions 1126, 1150, 1313 AFL-CIO, 1966- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Code no.5041: Metropolitan Taxicab Board of Trade and New York City Taxi Drivers Union, Local 3036, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Code no.5042: Yellow Cab Company and Checker Taxi Company and Democratic Union Organizing Committee, Local 777, Transportation Services and Allied Workers, Seafarers International Union, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Code no.5201: California Trucking Association, Inc. and International Association of Machinists, 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Code no.5204: Central Pennsylvania Motor Carriers Conference Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Local 229, 401, 429, 430, 764, 771, 773, 776, 1958-1967 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Code no.5206: Eastern Cement Haulers Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, 1959-1971 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Code no.5208: Empire State Highway Transportation Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 807, Truck Drivers Local Union, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Code no.5209: No Employer and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, National Master Automobile Transporters Agreement, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Code no.5210: No Employer and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Automobile Carrier Driveaway Agreement, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Code no.591401: No Employer and Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, Dry Cargo and Tanker District 1, Pacific Coast District, 1965- 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6301: Food Employers Council, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 630, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Code no.5404: No Employer and Seafarers International Union of North America, Atlantic, Gulf, Lakes, and Inland Waters District, 1970- 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Code no.5406: Esso Standard, Division of Humble Oil and Refining Company and Esso Seamen's Association, 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Code no.5407: Tanker Companies and National Maritime Union of America, 1958-1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Code no.5410: Pacific Maritime Association and International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots, 1965-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Code no.5412: Marine Towing and Transportation Employers' Association and National Maritime Union Local 333, United Marine Division, 1961-1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Code no.5414: Marine Towing and Transportation Employers' Association, Operators of Tugboats and Self-Propelled Lighters and National Maritime Union Local 333, United Marine Division, 1961-1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Code no.5416: Texas Ports and the Port of Lake Charles, LA and International Longshoremen's Association, South Atlantic and Gulf Coast District, 1956-1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Code no.5417: Hampton Roads Maritime Association and International Longshoremen's Association, 1959-1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Code no.5419: Mobile Steamship Association, Inc. and International Longshoremen's Association Local 1410, 1959-1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Code no.5421: New Orleans Steamship Association and General Longshore Workers Locals 1418 and 1419, 1959-1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Code no.5423: New York Shipping Association and International Longshoremen's Association, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Code no.5425: Philadelphia Marine Trade Association and International Longshoremen's Association, 1959-1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Code no.5426: Steamship Trade Association of Baltimore, Inc. and International Longshoremen's Association, 1964-1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Code no.5427: Steamship Trade Association of Baltimore, Inc. and International Longshoremen's Association, Locals 829, 858, 921, 953, 1355, and 1429, 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Code no.5248: Great Lakes Marine Operators and Seafarers International Union Great Lakes District, 1962-1971 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Code no.5430: West Gulf Maritime Association, Inc. and International Longshoremen's Association, South Atlantic and Gulf Coast District, 1968- 1971 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Code no.5430: Galveston Maritime Association, Inc., and Houston Maritime Association, Inc. and International Longshoremen's Association, South Atlantic and Gulf Coast District, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Code no.5431: Savannah Maritime Association and International Longshoremen's Association Locals 1414 and 1475, 1968-1974 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Code no.5015: Milwaukee and Suburban Transport Corporation and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 998, 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Code no.591342: Yellow Cab Company of Cleveland, Inc.; Zone Cab Corp.; Universal Cab Company; United Garage and Service Corporation of Cleveland, Ohio; Yellow Cab Limousines, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and H, 1959-1971 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Code no.5029: Yellow Cab Company of Philadelphia; Yellow Limousine Service, Inc. and Taxicab Drivers' Union, Local 156, 1969- 1973 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Code no.5222: No Employer and Chicago Truck Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers Union of Chicago and Vicinity (Independent), 1967- 1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Code no.5275: Merchants Fast Motor Lines, Inc. and Union of Transportation Employees, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Code no.5239: Truck Owners' Association of Seattle, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 174, 1967-1973 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Code no.590590: Pacific Maritime Association and National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, Pacific Coast District, 1956- 1960 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Code no.590491: Pacific Maritime Association and International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots, Local 90, 1964-1972 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Code no.5213: No Employer and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 710, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Code no.5214: National Master Freight Agreement and Over-the-Road and Local Cartage Employees of Private Common, Contract and Local Cartage Carriers, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Code no.5215: National Master Freight Agreement and New Jersey-New York Area Over-the-Road and Local Cartage Employees of Private Common, Contract and Local Cartage Carriers, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Code no.5217: Several Employers and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America Local 814, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Code no.5218: No Employer and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America - Central Conference of Teamsters, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)